{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow!' Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk!"},{"text":"🧶 I like to play with yarn!"},{"text":"🐈 I am a furry pet!"}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Woof!' Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I like to chew on bones!"},{"text":"🎾 I like to play fetch!"},{"text":"🐾 I wag my tail!"}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I go 'Baa!' and give you wool. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"☁️ My wool is fluffy!"},{"text":"🌾 I eat grass in a field!"},{"text":"🐑 I am a farm animal!"}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in the water. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧡 I have orange feet!"},{"text":"🦆 I have a bill!"},{"text":"💦 I love to be in a pond!"}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Frog","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I oink and love to roll in the mud. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐽 I have a snout!"},{"text":"🐖 I am often pink!"},{"text":"🏡 I live on a farm!"}],"options":[{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Mouse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Moo!' and give you milk. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐄 I am a big animal."},{"text":"🌱 I eat grass."},{"text":"🥛 You can drink what I make!"}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Donkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I hop and like to eat carrots. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I love orange vegetables!"},{"text":"🐰 I have long ears!"},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat in the garden!"}],"options":[{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Squirrel","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I love to eat peanuts!"},{"text":"🐘 I am very big!"},{"text":"🌍 I live in Africa and Asia."}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hippo","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I am the king of the jungle. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"👑 I have a big mane!"},{"text":"🐾 I am a cat, but very big!"},{"text":"🦁 I live in Africa."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Wolf","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I am green, hop, and say 'Ribbit'. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐛 I like to eat bugs!"},{"text":"🐸 I live near the water!"},{"text":"💦 I can swim."}],"options":[{"label":"Frog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lizard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}}],"cosmos":[{"level":"1","type":"cosmos","question":"I shine bright at night, but I'm not the moon. I twinkle! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✨ I am very far away."},{"text":"🌃 You can see many of me!"},{"text":"🌟 I am in the sky."}],"options":[{"label":"A cloud","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A star","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"2","type":"cosmos","question":"I am big and round and you live on me! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🏡 Your house is on me!"},{"text":"🌱 Plants grow on me!"},{"text":"💧 I have lots of water!"}],"options":[{"label":"The sun","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Earth","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A rocket","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"3","type":"cosmos","question":"I am very hot and give light to the Earth. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"☀️ I come out during the day."},{"text":"🔥 I am very, very hot!"},{"text":"🌻 Plants need me to grow."}],"options":[{"label":"The sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"The moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"4","type":"cosmos","question":"I am in the sky at night, and sometimes I'm round, sometimes I'm a crescent. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌙 Werewolves like me"},{"text":"🧀 Some people say I'm made of cheese"},{"text":"🌚 I don't shine my own light"}],"options":[{"label":"The sun","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The moon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A star","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"5","type":"cosmos","question":"We go around the sun, and the Earth is one of us. What are we called?","hints":[{"text":"🌎 Earth is one of us!"},{"text":"💫 We are in space!"},{"text":"🚶 We travel around the sun"}],"options":[{"label":"Clouds","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Planets","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Stars","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"6","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a big ball of gas that makes its own light, and many twinkle in the sky at night! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🔥 I am burning gas."},{"text":"✨I shine brightly"},{"text":"🌟The sun is one of me"}],"options":[{"label":"A planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A star","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A moon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"7","type":"cosmos","question":"I am a ride that takes people to space. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"👩‍🚀 Astronauts travel in me."},{"text":"🚀 I go very, very fast!"},{"text":"🌌 I leave the Earth!"}],"options":[{"label":"A car","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A rocket","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A boat","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"8","type":"cosmos","question":"I’m a group of stars that makes a picture in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐻 You can find me in the stars"},{"text":"🌠 I have a name"},{"text":"🔗 I connect the stars"}],"options":[{"label":"Galaxy","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Constellation","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Meteor","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"9","type":"cosmos","question":"I’m a place with many stars, planets, and space dust. I’m really, really big! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✨ I contain many stars"},{"text":"🌀 I'm shaped like a spiral sometimes!"},{"text":"🔭 The Milky Way is an example of me"}],"options":[{"label":"A planet","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A galaxy","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A comet","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"10","type":"cosmos","question":"I am made of ice and dust and have a long, bright tail when I get close to the sun. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"☄️ I'm a dirty snowball"},{"text":"☄️ I visit the Earth sometimes!"},{"text":"☄️ My tail points away from the sun"}],"options":[{"label":"A star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A comet","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A planet","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"cosmos","icon":"🌍"}}]}